<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sales Skills on How &amp; When</title>
    <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/tags/sales-skills/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sales Skills on How &amp; When</description>
    <image>
      <title>How &amp; When</title>
      <url>https://howard-haowen.github.io/profile.jpeg</url>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/profile.jpeg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.3</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://howard-haowen.github.io/tags/sales-skills/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IBM watsonx.ai Technical Sales Advanced</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx-ai-technical-sales-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx-ai-technical-sales-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates advanced knowledge and skills with watsonx.ai, and the ability to deliver client-facing Proof of Value projects.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/03c399fa-cde2-4426-aae6-2cb032cf5e2a/public_url">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Advanced Knowledge</strong>: Master watsonx.ai through comprehensive learning.</li>
<li><strong>Practical Skills</strong>: Develop the ability to define, build, and deliver a Proof of Concept (PoC).</li>
<li><strong>Client Success</strong>: Clearly and effectively demonstrate the value of IBM technology to clients.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification?</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Validated Expertise</strong>: Showcase advanced knowledge and skills in watsonx.ai.</li>
<li><strong>Proof of Value</strong>: Successfully deliver client-facing Proof of Value projects.</li>
<li><strong>Exceed Client Expectations</strong>: Demonstrate that IBM technology meets or exceeds client requirements.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/03c399fa-cde2-4426-aae6-2cb032cf5e2a/public_url">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM watsonx Orchestrate Sales Foudation</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx-orchestrate-sales-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx-orchestrate-sales-foundation/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates the understanding of IBM watsonx Orchestrate and the ability to articulate its value to customers.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/88be50b7-f15a-4aeb-9d5f-a0d13759011e/public_url">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Business Challenges</strong>: Reveal common business challenges during customer conversations.</li>
<li><strong>Orchestrate Solutions</strong>: Articulate how watsonx Orchestrate addresses and solves pain points.</li>
<li><strong>Competitive Edge</strong>: Know how to beat the competition with Watson&rsquo;s skills and integrations.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification?</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Fundamental Knowledge</strong>: Prove your understanding of IBM watsonx Orchestrate.</li>
<li><strong>Effective Teams</strong>: Streamline client efforts, making teams more effective.</li>
<li><strong>Customer Success</strong>: Help customers leverage Watson&rsquo;s skills and integrations.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/88be50b7-f15a-4aeb-9d5f-a0d13759011e/public_url">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM Sales Excellence Academy APAC</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-sales-excellence-academy-apac/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-sales-excellence-academy-apac/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates the seller&amp;#39;s ability to effectively leverage the IBM team, navigate the APAC sales process, and deliver client value through foundational product knowledge and sales tool proficiency.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/1e38ff69-ffa0-48b6-a50e-d72a54bfff4e/public_url">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Mastering the APAC Sales Rhythm</strong>:  Gain expertise in navigating the stages of the APAC sales process, from opportunity identification to closure.</li>
<li><strong>Building Strategic Partnerships</strong>: Learn to effectively collaborate with the broader IBM team and ecosystem partners to maximize client engagement.</li>
<li><strong>Delivering Client Value with IBM Solutions</strong>: Develop a foundational understanding of IBM products and sales tools to effectively present and sell solutions.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Become a High-Performing APAC Seller</strong>: Enhance your sales skills and contribute to significant revenue growth within the APAC region.</li>
<li><strong>Expand Your Professional Network</strong>:  Strengthen your collaboration skills and build relationships across the IBM ecosystem and with key clients.</li>
<li><strong>Increase Your Market Value</strong>: Differentiate yourself in the competitive sales landscape with specialized APAC sales expertise.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/1e38ff69-ffa0-48b6-a50e-d72a54bfff4e/public_url">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM watsonx.data Sales Foundation</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx.data-sales-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx.data-sales-foundation/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates an understanding of AI concepts, IBM&amp;#39;s AI strategy, the watsonx platform, and watsonx.data&amp;#39;s role in AI development and enterprise data management.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/8dc5bf09-0be2-468f-88dd-07bf3a5e2a93/public_url">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>AI Concepts</strong>: Understand the concepts and advantages of artificial intelligence (AI).</li>
<li><strong>IBM&rsquo;s AI Strategy</strong>: Grasp IBM&rsquo;s distinctive AI strategy for ethical and sustainable AI.</li>
<li><strong>watsonx Platform</strong>: Learn the significance of the watsonx AI and data platform.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification?</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Data Storage</strong>: Understand how watsonx.data fulfills data storage and processing requirements.</li>
<li><strong>Versatile Solution</strong>: Articulate how watsonx.data is a versatile solution for enterprise needs.</li>
<li><strong>Data Lakehouse</strong>: Master the data lakehouse functionality with watsonx.data.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/8dc5bf09-0be2-468f-88dd-07bf3a5e2a93/public_url">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM watsonx.governance Sales Foundation</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx.governance-sales-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx.governance-sales-foundation/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates a comprehensive understanding of AI governance, IBM&amp;#39;s AI strategy for ethical and sustainable AI, and the use of the watsonx.governance platform for enterprise-wide model management.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/61fe131e-70db-4574-8c35-8b534d626090/public_url">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn:**</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>AI Governance Fundamentals</strong>: Understand the core concepts and principles of artificial intelligence governance.</li>
<li><strong>IBM&rsquo;s AI Strategy</strong>: Grasp IBM&rsquo;s approach to addressing ethical and sustainable AI challenges.</li>
<li><strong>Mastering watsonx.governance</strong>: Learn to monitor, evaluate, and manage AI models using IBM&rsquo;s platform.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification:**</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Boost your AI credibility</strong>: Demonstrate your knowledge of responsible AI development and deployment.</li>
<li><strong>Gain a competitive edge</strong>: Showcase expertise in a leading AI governance platform.</li>
<li><strong>Future-proof your career</strong>: Prepare for the increasing demand for AI professionals with ethical considerations.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/61fe131e-70db-4574-8c35-8b534d626090/public_url">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM Global Sales School - Sales Activation</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-global-sales-school-sales-activation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-global-sales-school-sales-activation/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates the ability to effectively engage with clients, identify opportunities, and drive revenue growth through the development of key sales skills.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/0e04d6e3-c106-4fec-b794-60ba0bbfa56d/public_url">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn:</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Drive Client Conversations:</strong>  Master the art of engaging clients effectively, uncovering their needs, and building rapport.</li>
<li><strong>Research Client and Industry:</strong> Develop in-depth knowledge of client businesses and industries, allowing you to tailor your approach and identify opportunities.</li>
<li><strong>Leverage the IBM Client Engagement Model:</strong> Understand and apply IBM&rsquo;s structured approach to client engagement, maximizing success and achieving desired outcomes.</li>
<li><strong>Prospect and Identify Opportunities:</strong>  Become adept at identifying potential clients, understanding their pain points, and crafting compelling value propositions.</li>
<li><strong>Articulate Financial Value:</strong>  Learn to quantify the value of IBM solutions for clients, demonstrating the tangible benefits and return on investment.</li>
<li><strong>Develop a Competitive Mindset:</strong>  Gain the skills to confidently navigate competitive landscapes and differentiate IBM offerings effectively.</li>
<li><strong>Deliver Effective Presentations and Demonstrations:</strong>  Master the art of presenting IBM solutions persuasively, engaging audiences, and driving action.</li>
<li><strong>Prepare to Negotiate:</strong>  Develop strong negotiation skills to secure favorable outcomes and close deals successfully.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification:</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Enhance your sales skills and knowledge:</strong>  Acquire the core competencies necessary for success in the IBM sales environment.</li>
<li><strong>Differentiate yourself as a sales professional:</strong>  Demonstrate your commitment to professional development and proficiency in best-practice sales methodologies.</li>
<li><strong>Grow revenue and achieve sales targets:</strong>  Apply your newly acquired skills to drive client engagement, identify opportunities, and achieve sales goals.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/0e04d6e3-c106-4fec-b794-60ba0bbfa56d/public_url">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM watsonx.ai Technical Sales Intermediate</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx.ai-technical-sales-intermediate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx.ai-technical-sales-intermediate/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates the ability to discuss the value proposition of IBM watsonx.ai with clients, demonstrating an understanding of its generative AI and foundation model capabilities as well as its key features through hands-on experience.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/7e249201-e500-49e2-b883-b8b3daa0d6a8/public_url">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Hands-on watsonx.ai Experience</strong>: Gain practical, hands-on experience using IBM&rsquo;s watsonx.ai platform for generative AI and foundation model capabilities.</li>
<li><strong>watsonx.ai Architecture &amp; Strategy</strong>: Develop a comprehensive understanding of watsonx.ai&rsquo;s architecture and how it integrates into IBM&rsquo;s overall AI strategy.</li>
<li><strong>Effective Client Communication</strong>: Learn to articulate the value proposition of watsonx.ai to clients, highlighting its key features and benefits.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Become a watsonx.ai Practitioner</strong>: Demonstrate practical expertise in leveraging watsonx.ai for generative AI solutions.</li>
<li><strong>Gain a Competitive Edge:</strong>  Showcase your hands-on experience with a leading AI platform, enhancing your marketability.</li>
<li><strong>Drive Client Engagement</strong>: Develop the communication skills needed to effectively present and sell the value of watsonx.ai.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/7e249201-e500-49e2-b883-b8b3daa0d6a8/public_url">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM watsonx.ai Generative AI Tools Sales Foundation</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx.ai-generative-ai-tools-sales-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx.ai-generative-ai-tools-sales-foundation/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates the skills to utilize watsonX.ai for efficient and trustworthy business applications, including model training and building trust with stakeholders.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/275d0bcc-bb2e-4323-b4a8-2235032adda6/public_url">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>watsonx.ai Fundamentals</strong>: Develop a strong understanding of the core concepts, advantages, and capabilities of the IBM watsonx.ai platform and its generative AI tools.</li>
<li><strong>Foundation Model Exploitation</strong>: Learn how to leverage foundation models within watsonx.ai to address diverse business use cases effectively.</li>
<li><strong>Enterprise AI Deployment</strong>: Understand how watsonx.ai addresses enterprise needs related to model training, trust, and efficiency in business applications.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Become a watsonx.ai Proficient</strong>: Demonstrate your expertise in utilizing IBM&rsquo;s watsonx.ai platform for generative AI solutions.</li>
<li><strong>Unlock Foundation Model Power</strong>: Learn to harness the power of foundation models to drive innovation and efficiency within your organization.</li>
<li><strong>Build Trustworthy AI Solutions</strong>: Develop the skills to build and deploy reliable and trustworthy AI applications that meet enterprise needs.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/275d0bcc-bb2e-4323-b4a8-2235032adda6/public_url">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM watsonx.ai Sales Foundation</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx.ai-sales-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx.ai-sales-foundation/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates a comprehensive grasp of IBM&amp;#39;s ethical AI approach and the capabilities of WatsonX.ai for rapid and trustworthy AI application development.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/9cd23844-f6e4-4bb0-946d-37a4bb1b8c77/public_url">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>AI Fundamentals &amp; IBM&rsquo;s Strategy</strong>: Understand core AI concepts and IBM&rsquo;s approach to ethical and sustainable AI development.</li>
<li><strong>watsonx AI Platform Proficiency</strong>:  Gain knowledge of the watsonx AI and data platform, focusing on its capabilities for rapid AI application development.</li>
<li><strong>Enterprise AI Deployment</strong>: Learn how watsonx.ai addresses enterprise needs for efficient model training and trustworthy, efficient business applications.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Become an IBM watsonx AI Expert:</strong> Demonstrate proficiency in using IBM&rsquo;s leading AI platform for building and deploying AI solutions.</li>
<li><strong>Accelerate AI Development:</strong> Learn to rapidly build and deploy AI applications using the integrated capabilities of watsonx.ai.</li>
<li><strong>Build Trustworthy Enterprise AI:</strong>  Understand how to address ethical considerations and build reliable AI solutions that meet enterprise needs.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/9cd23844-f6e4-4bb0-946d-37a4bb1b8c77/public_url">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM watsonx Essentials</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx-essentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/ibm-watsonx-essentials/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates expertise in deploying AI with IBM watsonx, emphasizing responsible workflows and ethical considerations.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/3ab6a975-13c4-4b12-ab66-3e93c7f8da54/public_url">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>IBM watsonx Generative AI Deployment</strong>: Understand how to deploy and embed generative AI solutions across various business functions using the IBM watsonx platform.</li>
<li><strong>Data Management &amp; Responsible AI</strong>: Learn how to manage diverse data sources and accelerate responsible AI workflows within the IBM watsonx ecosystem.</li>
<li><strong>IBM&rsquo;s AI Strategy</strong>: Gain insight into IBM&rsquo;s approach to addressing ethical and sustainable challenges in the development and deployment of AI.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Become an IBM watsonx Expert</strong>: Showcase your understanding of IBM&rsquo;s leading AI platform and its capabilities in generative AI.</li>
<li><strong>Drive Business Value with AI</strong>: Learn how to leverage generative AI to solve real-world business problems and create competitive advantage.</li>
<li><strong>Champion Responsible AI</strong>: Demonstrate your commitment to ethical and sustainable AI practices, a key differentiator in today&rsquo;s market.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/3ab6a975-13c4-4b12-ab66-3e93c7f8da54/public_url">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
