<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CognitiveClass on How &amp; When</title>
    <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/tags/cognitiveclass/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CognitiveClass on How &amp; When</description>
    <image>
      <title>How &amp; When</title>
      <url>https://howard-haowen.github.io/profile.jpeg</url>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/profile.jpeg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.3</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://howard-haowen.github.io/tags/cognitiveclass/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CognitiveClass Big Data Foundations</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/cognitive-class-big-data-foundations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/cognitive-class-big-data-foundations/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates the expertise in big data technologies, demonstrating the ability to harness the power of Hadoop and Spark for efficient data processing and analysis.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.credly.com/badges/8e195098-81f2-4cb2-8dcb-50883a78cdc8/public_url">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<p>To earn this certification, you need to complete a learning path that covers the following three courses:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Hadoop 101</strong>: This beginner Apache Hadoop course introduces you to Big Data concepts, and teaches you how to perform distributed processing of large data sets with Hadoop.</li>
</ul>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="/certifications/cognitive-class-big-data-foundations/ibm-hadoop-101.png"></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Spark Fundamentals I</strong>: Ignite your interest in Spark with an introduction to the core concepts that make this general processor an essential tool set for working with Big Data.</li>
</ul>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="/certifications/cognitive-class-big-data-foundations/ibm-spark-fundamentals-1.png"></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Big Data 101</strong>: How big is big and why does big matter and what does Apache Hadoop have to do with it? In this course you will see the Big Data big picture and you will learn the terminology used in Big Data discussions.</li>
</ul>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="/certifications/cognitive-class-big-data-foundations/ibm-big-data-101.png"></p>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn:</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Big Data Ecosystem:</strong> Gain a comprehensive understanding of the big data ecosystem, its components, and key concepts.</li>
<li><strong>Hadoop Fundamentals:</strong> Learn how to use Hadoop commands and operations for processing large datasets in a distributed environment.</li>
<li><strong>Spark Core Concepts:</strong> Master the core concepts of Apache Spark, including RDDs, DataFrames, and its various libraries.</li>
<li><strong>Spark Libraries:</strong> Develop proficiency in working with Spark libraries like MLlib (machine learning), Spark SQL (data querying), Spark Streaming (real-time data processing), and GraphX (graph processing).</li>
<li><strong>Practical Application:</strong> Apply your knowledge through hands-on exercises and projects using Hadoop and Spark.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification:</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Become a Big Data Expert:</strong> Develop a solid foundation in the big data landscape, equipping you to handle massive datasets.</li>
<li><strong>Master Hadoop and Spark:</strong> Gain in-depth knowledge of Hadoop and Spark, two essential tools for big data processing.</li>
<li><strong>Unlock Career Opportunities:</strong> Prepare for high-demand roles in big data analysis, data engineering, and related fields.</li>
<li><strong>Stay Ahead of the Data Revolution:</strong> Equip yourself with the skills necessary to navigate the rapidly growing field of big data.</li>
<li><strong>Solve Real-World Problems:</strong> Learn how to leverage big data technologies to address complex challenges and extract valuable insights.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://cognitiveclass.ai/learn/big-data">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CognitiveClass Python 101 for Data Science</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/cognitive-class-python101-for-data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/cognitive-class-python101-for-data-science/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates foundational Python programming skills, preparing earners for data science and various programming roles.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://courses.cognitiveclass.ai/certificates/9e992d6605644ef78e617e18fd293b0c">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Python Programming Unlocked</strong>: Learn the fundamentals of Python programming from scratch, even with no prior experience.</li>
<li><strong>Rapid Python Proficiency</strong>:  Go from zero to writing your own Python scripts in a short amount of time.</li>
<li><strong>Data Analysis Introduction</strong>: Get started with basic hands-on data analysis using a Jupyter-based lab environment.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Launch Your Data Science Journey</strong>: Build a strong foundation in Python, essential for a career in data science.</li>
<li><strong>Become a Python Programmer</strong>:  Gain practical skills to write your own Python scripts and solve problems.</li>
<li><strong>Unlock Coding Potential</strong>:  Develop valuable programming skills applicable across various domains.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://cognitiveclass.ai/courses/python-for-data-science">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CognitiveClass Prompt Engineering for Everyone</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/cognitive-class-prompt-engineering-for-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/cognitive-class-prompt-engineering-for-everyone/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates skills in harnessing the power of AI through effective prompt engineering, demonstrating the ability to communicate complex ideas to AI systems and control the style, tone, and content of AI responses.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://courses.cognitiveclass.ai/certificates/739fdebcb9dc4f3b8311d9a304bb68f1">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn:</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Fundamentals of Prompt Engineering:</strong> Understand the concept of prompt engineering and its importance in AI interaction.</li>
<li><strong>Prompt Engineering Techniques:</strong> Learn various techniques for crafting effective prompts, including the Naive Prompting Approach, Persona Pattern, Interview Pattern, Chain-of-Thought Approach, and Tree-of-Thought Approach.</li>
<li><strong>Controlling AI Responses:</strong> Acquire skills to control the verbosity and style of AI responses using methods like the Nova System.</li>
<li><strong>Utilizing Watsonx Prompt Lab:</strong> Gain hands-on experience with the powerful watsonx Prompt Lab tool.</li>
<li><strong>Language Proficiency:</strong> Develop the ability to effectively communicate with AI systems using both English and your native language.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification:</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Unlock AI&rsquo;s Full Potential:</strong> Learn to leverage AI&rsquo;s capabilities for enhanced productivity and creativity.</li>
<li><strong>Master AI Communication:</strong> Become a proficient AI communicator, crafting prompts that yield accurate and insightful responses.</li>
<li><strong>Improve AI Interactions:</strong> Enhance the efficacy of your interactions with AI systems through effective prompting strategies.</li>
<li><strong>Stay Ahead of the Curve:</strong> Acquire a valuable skill in high demand as AI becomes increasingly integrated into various industries.</li>
<li><strong>Unlock New Opportunities:</strong> Gain a competitive advantage in the digital age by mastering the art of prompt engineering.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://cognitiveclass.ai/courses/prompt-engineering-for-everyone">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CognitiveClass the Art of Prompt Engineering</title>
      <link>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/cognitive-class-the-art-of-prompt-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://howard-haowen.github.io/certifications/cognitive-class-the-art-of-prompt-engineering/</guid>
      <description>Earning this certification validates the expertise in crafting effective prompts, leveraging AI models and the Python Langchain library for practical applications.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://courses.cognitiveclass.ai/certificates/0597a0bcb8bd4152bb0490ede959163a">Certification URL</a></p>
<h2 id="certification-details">Certification details</h2>
<h3 id="what-you-will-learn">What you will learn</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Mastering Prompt Engineering</strong>:  Understand the core principles of prompt engineering and its crucial role in optimizing AI tools.</li>
<li><strong>Effective Prompt Crafting</strong>: Develop skills to create high-performing prompts for enhanced AI model output.</li>
<li><strong>Langchain Proficiency</strong>: Gain hands-on experience using the Langchain library for prompt engineering tasks.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-earn-this-certification">Why earn this certification</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>Boost AI Tool Efficiency</strong>: Learn to significantly improve the performance of AI tools like chatbots and content generators.</li>
<li><strong>Practical Application in Python</strong>: Develop practical skills through a Python project applying prompt engineering principles to survival analysis.</li>
<li><strong>Enhance Data Analysis Capabilities</strong>:  Improve your data analysis skills by leveraging the power of prompt engineering.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://cognitiveclass.ai/courses/the-art-of-prompt-engineering">Source</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
